A romantic comedy with commitment issues.
Sleeping with Other People is a comedy, romance
film directed by Leslye Headland.
Can two serial cheaters get a second chance at love?
After a one-night stand in college, New Yorkers Lainey and Jake meet by chance twelve years later and discover they each
have the same problem: because of their monogamy-challenged ways, neither can maintain a relationship.
Determined to stay friends despite their mutual attraction, they make a pact
to keep it platonic, a deal that proves easier said than done.
Jake Harper, played by Jason Sudeikis.
Lainey Dalton, played by Alison Brie.
Matthew Sobvechik, played by Adam Scott.
Xander, played by Jason Mantzoukas.
Kara, played by Natasha Lyonne.
Sam, played by Adam Brody.
Sleeping with Other People is a 2015 American romantic comedy
film written and directed by Leslye Headland.
The film stars Jason Sudeikis, Alison Brie, Natasha
Lyonne, Amanda Peet, and Adam Scott.
Premiering at the Sundance Film Festival on January 24, 2015, the film was
released theatrically on September 11, 2015, by IFC Films.
Sleeping with Other People received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, cheating,
loss of virginity, womanizer, love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.